Usage: act [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]...

Nova Act CLI - Deploy Python workflows to AWS AgentCore Runtime.

A streamlined CLI for deploying Python scripts and projects to AWS AgentCore
with automatic containerization, ECR management, and multi-region support.

QUICK START:

    # Deploy any Python script in one command
    act workflow deploy --source-dir /path/to/your/code

    # Run the deployed workflow
    act workflow run --name <generated-name> --payload '{"input": "data"}'

FEATURES:

    - Quick deploy: Deploy scripts without pre-configuration
    - Auto-containerization: Automatic Docker image building
    - ECR management: Automatic repository creation and image pushing
    - IAM integration: Automatic role creation and management
    - Multi-region: Deploy to any AWS region
    - Workflow tracking: Persistent configuration management

REQUIREMENTS:

    - AWS CLI configured with appropriate permissions
    - Docker installed and running
    - Python 3.10+ environment
    - IAM permissions for ECR, AgentCore, and IAM operations

CONFIGURATION:

Workflows are stored in region-specific directories under C:\Users\jamat\.act_cli\state with support for
multiple regions and deployment tracking.

For detailed command help, use: act workflow --help

Options:
  --version  Show the version and exit.
  --help     Show this message and exit.

Commands:
  workflow     Workflow management commands for AWS AgentCore deployment.
